Entonces...
When you little baby dinos...
How to play
passion convincingly?
What can I say?
I don't know.
But...
This stage will kill me.
I can show you the way.
And everything that happens
next will be your own story.
Your own way to act.
Okay?
Nice.
So all I need now is
one brave heart
that can shout FREEDOM
and free itself.
Again, no?
Still no?
Come on, folks.
Come on.
Come on, guys.
I don't know.
Okay.
One and only,
magnificent Gina Rose.
Now, the important thing.
Gina,
do you feel safe right now?
Yes.
Can I touch you with
my hands and my lips?
Of course, you can.
Good. Nice.
Passion,
the little baby dinos,
is not about banging
all night in the boudoir.
Passion
is about restraint,
about taboo.
I want to kiss her so much.
The tension makes
makes my lips tremble.